♪Love's little quiz
takes seven parts sweet♪
♪And three parts bitter,
till you and I meet♪
♪I pretend I'm not there,
but secretly stay♪
♪Waiting for you♪
♪We've got so many
romantic dreams to unfold♪
♪Finally hearing
the I love you I long to hold♪
♪Falling fast
into the swirl of your eyes♪
♪It's just too tempting, so tempting♪
♪Never could I have guessed♪
♪My heart's rhythm♪
♪How beautiful it is, meeting you♪
=Late to Love=
(Adapted from "My Husband Is A Billionaire!")
=Episode 22=
That's amazing.
Doesn't that mean...
We've got this in the bag.
Then our wedding day
will basically be Ye Group's funeral.
Talk about a double celebration.
That sounds a little weird, doesn't it?
Yeah, it's a little weird.
Doesn't matter.
But I still feel
it's not enough.
In the end, we need to make sure their crimes
are splashed across every headline.
We need to make the whole world
know everything Ye Group did.
Why do you think I reached out
to that famous emcee
to host our wedding?
She actually said yes?
Of course.
She started out
in investigative journalism.
She hates dirty laundry.
That's amazing.
Cheers.
Alright.
Now we just wait for Dr. X
to work her magic.
Don't worry.
We'll have the results by tomorrow.
Don't stay up
too late tonight.
Well, tonight,
I actually have a surprise for you.
♪All of my dreams, leading me here♪
♪Fueling the fire
that help me fight all the fear♪
♪All that I've got, and all that I am♪
♪All that I gave up
just to stand where I stand♪
♪Every step that I took was toward you♪
How do I look?
♪Someone I've been looking for♪
♪Don't have to keep searching anymore♪
Perfect.
Flawless.
♪But everything changed,
and anything is possible♪
♪I found what I've been looking for♪
(With a wedding thrown)
(on this grand a scale,)
(no way this is
just about getting married.)
(What on earth are they planning?)
(Xu Nange,)
(where on earth are you?)
(Bodyguard)
Hello?
Mr. Zichen,
we've tracked down
where Xu Nange is hiding.
Where is she?
Send me the address.
Right now!
Yes, sir.
We found her.
Destroy the lab data
and lock her down completely.
You're not going soft
on Xu Nange, are you?
Huo Zichen, this is our one shot.
Don't mess up now.
Don't forget.
You're the one who wanted Huo Group
to get back at Beiyan.
Don't worry.
I know what to do.
(It worked.)
(After all these years,)
(I finally got)
(the validation results I needed.)
(After all the hard work and sacrifice,)
(this exact moment)
(makes it all worth it.)
(Ye Xin,)
(I will absolutely
bring you to justice.)
Mr. Zichen,
we've checked
everywhere we can.
There's no sign of Xu Nange.
The apartment is the only place left.
But when we got here,
the front door was locked.
It doesn't look like
anyone's been staying here.
Break the lock.
Get in there and search the place.
I'm almost there.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Zichen,
this place really doesn't look lived in.
It was like this when we broke in.
Are you messing with me?
Mr. Zichen, please believe me.
I really saw
Mr. Huo heading this way.
Hello, Mr. Zichen?
Hello?
Hello, Mr. Huo?
Someone's tracking you.
Guess the apartment
isn't safe anymore either.
Got it.
Get a few guys over here to pack up.
We're moving.
Mr. Huo, Nange,
what a wonderful surprise.
I'm so sorry for the poor reception.
I didn't have anything prepared.
Please don't hold it against me.
It's fine.
Mrs. Xu.
(Wedding)
This is the invitation to our wedding.
When the day comes,
I really hope you and Xu Yin
can make it.
My gosh.
Coming all this way
just to drop off an invitation?
You could've just had
one of your people bring it over.
Well, you did raise Nange
for all those years after all.
It's the least I can do.
Nange,
has Mr. Huo
finally accepted our family?
Don't call me Mr. Huo.
Just Beiyan is fine.
Beiyan.
Beiyan it is.
I'll leave you two to chat.
I'm going to the restroom.
Go ahead.
Mrs. Xu, there's one more thing
I might need to trouble you with.
Before the wedding,
Nange might need
to stay here at your place
for a few days.
Is that alright?
Did something happen?
Shen Yan.
Mrs. Xu,
here's the thing.
Mr. and Mrs. Huo
are usually incredibly busy.
So they want to find
a quiet place
to prepare the wedding.
They don't want a bunch
of gossip tabloids bothering them
or reporters
hounding Mrs. Huo.
So if you could
do them this favor,
Huo Group
will definitely remember your kindness.
No need to be so polite.
Nange is my daughter.
According to tradition,
it's only right that she gets married
from her family home.
Don't worry.
Nange can stay right here with me.
I promise I'll keep her hidden.
Nobody is going to bother her.
And any updates whatsoever...
I won't reveal anything.
Thank you, Mrs. Xu.
Alright. You two make
yourselves comfortable.
I'm going
to get Nange's room ready
and put some fresh sheets on her bed.
I should get going.
Beiyan,
hold on.
Are you seriously
not worried about Li Wanru?
She used to be pretty tight
with Huo Zichen.
Don't worry.
She's smart.
She knows which way the wind is blowing.
She knows whose side to be on right now.
Well,
since you have me hiding out here,
Huo Zichen and Ye Xin
can't track me down.
Will you be in trouble?
Don't worry.
Just remember.
No matter what happens,
protect your final research data.
Also,
I might be tied up with other things
for the next three days.
I won't be able to drop by.
Take good care of yourself.
Don't worry.
I'll look after myself.
I'm off.
Is he even showing up today or what?
This is a total joke.
Shen Yan,
is Mr. Huo actually
coming to the meeting?
Deepest apologies, everyone.
Today's board meeting
will be chaired
by Old Mr. Huo for the time being.
Wait.
What?
I honestly thought
I could finally
enjoy my retirement in peace.
That's why I felt comfortable
handing the reins
of the company
over to you younger generation.
I never would've guessed
that during my time away,
Huo Group
has bred so many corporate parasites,
forming cliques
and hurting the company.
And worst of all,
trying to shake
the very foundation of Huo Group.
Do you all really think I'm too old
to clean house anymore?
Old Mr. Huo,
forming cliques
and hurting the company?
You can't just throw accusations
around like that.
Yeah.
Shen Yan.
Based on the audit,
Mr. Zhao,
Mr. Wang,
Mr. Li,
and 14 others, totaling 17 people,
abused their positions
to secretly collude with Ye Group,
embezzle company assets,
and leak core company secrets.
(Investigation Report on Major
Internal Misconduct Within Huo Group)
The evidence is solid.
(Investigation Report on Major
Internal Misconduct Within Huo Group)
Effective immediately,
the individuals mentioned
are stripped of all duties
and removed from Huo Group.
Everyone involved
will be handed over
to the authorities for prosecution.
Huo Group
will absolutely not tolerate
corporate parasites.
Gentlemen.
Please leave.
♪What destiny brought us to meet♪
♪Two different worlds, a love so sweet♪
♪A wish we made
in a past life, it seems♪
♪Destined to cross time and dream ♪
♪Like a fairytale story told♪
♪A gentle breeze feels so bold♪
♪As your hair brushes past your ear♪
♪I long to kiss your cheek, my dear♪
♪All my longing, all my love for you♪
♪Has never changed, it's forever true♪
♪It's the hand of fate
that we meet again♪
♪Let me hold you once again♪
♪Resting against your chest♪
♪Your warmth shines like stars at night♪
♪Let me kiss you once again♪
♪No reason needed♪
♪My heart belongs to you♪
♪I'm not afraid
to cross time to find you♪